Speed is very important
when you're driving...
...but must control it accurately
with courage and driving skill,
don't you know?
You see I've offend my hands.
So you learn how to balance.
Eyes looking forward,
backward and two sides
Keep watching all around you.
Maddie, I root you,
defeat that rich guy for me.
What time did you fix with him?
At 12, he's late, what's on?
Maybe that guy is too scared to come.
Damn you!
You're late, why not come next year?
No one ever dare to reprimand me, right?
Yes!
OK, Boss, let me handle.
I recognize you, Maddie, I remember...
You're...brother of that Dare Devil,
the prisoner.
Don't bullshit
Who are you?
I'm Fat C, what's your name?
Why only tell me now?
You don't have ask me, I'm Tse.
Don't bullshit, we'll know
who the winner is after the race.
Like Boss like dog.
He is a real flatter.
Sure, his head is big enough to bullshit.
...and not like you
You are so weak.
Your boss give you dog feed
to keep you so fat?
Have you taken money?
We bet on $300 thousand tonight.
Damn, get lost! $300 thousand?
Let's bet on $1 million full.
You boast! $1 million?
If I had $1 million,
I needn't race with you.
Right, you don't have, but I do.
You get the money if you win.
but if I win, I want no money.
What do you want then?
You're strong enough.
I want it!
You're afraid?
Don't be afraid
Let's go
I can't help if you must make me win.
Paddy.
Where's my motor-bike?
The real Chariot of Fire.
It's superb.
Give me.
Be careful.
Boss says he'll be happy
if you perform well!
Thanks.
He'll give some to each of you.
Call us if there's such
benefit next time.
Well, to him money is not an object.
but I'm the only flatter around him.
If you like, come here more often.
and do some help or root us.
Yes, promise, thanks.
Dee, is Big Head ready?
Get into position.
You must make a perfect comment.
...just like the car race
commentator on TV, OK?
Sure, will be like live show.
Paddy.
Is it OK?
Just perfect.
Really?
Give way! The Boss has come!
Boss.
Is it OK?
My Boss is mighty.
How come I'll make my Boss lose face?
Ready, start!
Dee, it has started.
Remember, report if anything happens.
Roger.
Really like flying!
They've arrived gas station
of Clear Water Bay Road.
If Sky did not fooling...
...he'd have lead by quite a distance.
I'll hand to the next stand.
Now they're racing on.
It's really interesting.
The road becomes their racing track.
Maddie is strong too, not bad.
Defeat Sky...
What are you looking, little girl?
I have bet on,
so I must know the result.
They're entering Junk Bay Tunnel.
Sky and Maddie are both trying
to surpass the other.
I wonder how many times
they have changed gear.
It's a Porsche, it's really fast, nuts!
Shit, the Porsche is ahead of Sky now!
I wish I could smash its windscreen.
He deserves capsizing!
Out the tunnel now,
Sky changes to 3rd gear.
He'll surpass me soon!
Sky, defeat Maddie...
Who are you?
What?
Shit! You lunatic!
Boss is smart!
Boss is the winner!
OK, $1 million, give me 2 month time.
I have money?
We agree to side bet on your leg.
Don't be too much
It's our agreement and stake,
don't you know?
Since you agree,
you must keep your words.
Boss
Don't be so much
No, if we must play,
we must play till the end.
You can't step on the accelerator
from now on.
Spanner!
Here
Where's Paddy?
Knock on him
Why? Let's break his leg.
Sky...
Don't you know how to?
You can't knock his leg,
but can repair cars?
It's...like this, to break his leg!
Boss...
We must keep the promise
of what we have said.
Boss, you're leaving?
You're on my bed,
what are you going to do?
The warden knows I love sleeping,
she won't suspect.
Thanks for helping me again.
Do you see Sky? He won or lost?
Of course, Sky is the winner.
That Maddie dare tell others
he's the Dare Devil.
How far away did he win? Tell me.
It's a motor-bike race.
It only takes 3 seconds
to reach 100 k.p.h.
What then? Tell me.
When I arrived,
I saw Sky on that motor-bike.
He's so cool!
Only that motor-bike can match Sky.
Do you know how powerful
that motor-bike is?
Don't know.
Do you know what means
by ''Double Speed''?
No idea And Quadrate Speed?
What is it? Tell me.
Let me take you to meet my dream lover
Great!
Does your dream lover have big eyes?
And how tall is he? Tell us.
What does he look like?
Is he handsome? Tell us.
Why don't you say?
Paddy.
Thanks.
I say Sky is a bit too much on that.
Too much of what?
I mean his side bet
with Maddie would be a leg.
It's too much to break
the opponent's leg.
But they mutually agreed.
This world talks of money.
I have to go,
stay here and fool with him.
Paddy...don't go,
the Boss hasn't let you leave yet.
He'll reduce your salary.
Look...
I'm happy today.
Your tips.
Why? The price for having sex with you?
I was only joking.
Don't you remember what day is today?
What day?
I was injured...6 years ago.
Why I never see your parents?
She hasn't come, look at this card.
Recover soon, Mom.
I know it's written by others.
Is it OK, I am here.
OK.
Come on, quick.
Come on.
Turn your face first.
OK.
Sky, your mom has just called up.
...saying that she'll pick you up
for dinner after the meeting.
Dinner will start at 7 sharp,
as she has another meeting at 8.
Forget the dinner.
Ask her to stick to the meetings.
That policeman will not charge you
for careless driving.
as your mom has settled the case.
Sure, the kid shouldn't
have rushed out to the road.
His parents should teach him
road safety instead.
That kid...
...died last night.
I've forgotten all the unhappy incidents
What will you...send me next year?
Next year?
I don't want
No?
Let's see next year
I don't want!
You don't want?
You know what I love most
Cars, and you
Hello! You've come home?
How's granny?
I have medical appointment at
Princess Mary Hospital tomorrow.
Don't go there, go to a private hospital.
It's chronic disease.
I know, I'll foot the bill, OK?
Sleep early
I love the bracelet you sent me.
Do you? Put it on then.
Good night, bye.
I know, the National Bureau
is strict on foreign investment.
but if you are able to help me,
everything should be fine.
You mom has just signed an agreement
with a Chinese Group.
if we make it, I'll buy you a car.
Uncle Sam's Ferrari 360...
...is laid off,
as his driver licence got suspended.
I'll buy it for you.
It's a limited edition,
only 30 worldwide.
None of my business,
I don't want a used car
I know you don't want a used car.
OK, let me order a brand new one for you.
Does my mom know?
No problem.
Don't look back, if you do,
it means you'll come here again.
I've been here 5 years,
I'm beginning to like it here.
You are not bad.
Others come here for a penalty, but you
studied and get several degrees in here.
So HK Government
is nice to bastards like you.
This is for you.
Read more, but not the comics.
or you'll spend the rest of your life here,
like the prisoners.
Brother Fung! Brother Fung!
Brother!
Why, you had an accident?
Don't tell others you're
my blood brother.
Not an accident,
he lost a race and the opponent broke it
It's that dude, Sky.
That guy even says Tang Fung is outdated.
...that he gets too clumsy for car racing.
Look how cocky he is!
He also advises you to retire.
Mind your saliva spoiling my engine.
This is lubricant.
It'll speed up the car instead.
Come and listen to the sound
of the accelerator.
Step on the accelerator OK, mechanic.
Classics...
It's enough, take it.
Pentium II 400, 300Mhz.
Thank you!
Throw away your outdated computer now.
Can you manage?
Yes.
I'll see...this is heart.
Nothing.
Healthy, Boss.
This is kidney...is it OK, Boss?
Nothing.
Boss, you're healthy, you have employ
two competent guys here.
Paddy is expert of checking engines.
and I am expert of checking your health.
boss, this is the sex organ...
Is it OK, Boss?
Boss...
Are you mistaken?
Beat it.
Boss is healthy and
has a powerful sex organ.
Hit my stick hard.
Boss is great!
Boss, have some water.
You left hospital so soon?
You can walk?
You take your uncle with you?
He is my brother...Tang Fung
You're Sky?
Not a good guy.
You side bet on his leg?
Let's clear things up,
it's mutual agreement.
Right, Tang Fung?
You were apprentice at 14
and started racing in 1982.
in 1983, no one could
follow you by 2 minutes.
From Princess Road to Clear Water Bay.
the fastest time
is 15 minutes 28 seconds.
You might finish university
if you studied as hard.
then your mom would be happy.
I'm better than you
You rose to top in 1988,
but you were too greedy.
you conspired with robbers
and were sent to jail.
after being released,
you commit a crime again...
I wonder if you like jail life.
Kid, I know you take me as idol,
like many others do.
Sorry, I don't admire you.
I just read it, take it as a souvenir.
You're son of Black Tone?
Dad, quick...
You know
how your dad got defeated by me?
You're much inferior than him indeed.
You think you're superior,
just because you're rich.
You think you can become the best car
racer with your money.
but you won't succeed as
you never improve yourself.
Want to challenge me?
I come to teach you something.
Cylinder head, change the gasket 1.6mm.
Decrease the compression ratio,
Turbo mark up to 1.5 bar.
Also need turbo exhaust manifold,
70mm front pipe.
and titanium metal exhausted
air tube at the rear.
Oil-suspension cooler,
and shock absorbers.
and use 14K spring.
Fix STI power lock and clutch.
Also install Mines racing computer,
then it can be called a car.
Quote me the price.
This only provides 300 hp at the maximum.
so be sure you can control it.
Sorry, we never modify Sabaru.
You won't or you dare not?
I don't want to,
but I want to race with you.
I like this, how to?
We can bet on whatever the stake is.
I don't want money,
I want a garage to mod Sabaru.
This is not a bad one.
Uncle, you get nuts in jail?
Boss's garage is worth $3 million?
And your stake?
My hand, if you want, both my hands.
Don't you like side bet on other's limbs?
OK, Friday night.
at 9:30 pm, at Kwun Tong Pier.
See you.
Sure.
Boss, have tea.
Don't let saliva come down
like him. Your saliva.
Mind your saliva.
Go, go on.
No drink allowed here.
None of your business I don't mean you.
Sir, don't you hear?
I'm not drinking now!
What's wrong with you?
What do you up to?
What're you going to do?
Take this and clean your head.
The clothes are dirty,
they need cleaning too.
They scared the customers,
ask them to leave.
It's fine then, go ahead.
Don't you know you follow me?
I'm playing with it, you cut the line?
I really didn't mean to.
What's happened?
This bitch.
...wants to cut the line,
when I'm playing
You, say sorry.
What is it?
Nothing, I'm playing with it
and she said I cut the line.
You hold her tight?
She's your girlfriend?
Kid, what girl? Are you of age?
I can kill you!
Kill me?
Take it easy, don't stir up trouble!
Do you know who he is?
He's Brother Sky, Dare devil!
Hurrah, Brother Sky!
Dare Devil? You know who I am?
Who are you?
I'm God of Car in this game centre.
They call me Sugihara Takuumi.
Brother Takuumi It's Brother Takuumip.
A Japanese?
What's that got to do with you?
You know who we are?
I'm called Big Head.
I'm called Dee.
Big Head, Dee, without us,
there won't be you, Takuuim?
I'll take you as of age, let's race.
Sure.
Don't bullshit, let's race now.
You are very lucky today.
Brother Sky is racing with you,
no problem.
Brother Sky will surely win.
You must lick my toes if you lose.
Lick the toes!
Shit, he's better than me.
Why? What's wrong with you?
Young man, calm down, take it easy!
I want to ask why the power
was suddenly cut off.
we've just taken the lead.
You boast? What shall we do now?
What shall we do?
It's your place here,
and you are God of Car, you suggest.
Nuts!
We're taking the lead.
Brother, what are you doing?
You helped your idol to cheat?
OK, forget it! It's a tie!
OK, when you grow up...
...I'll race with you on Princess Road.
Get lost.
Come for Brother Sky
when you grow up!
Beat it, if you are afraid.
Brother Sky.
You have released?
Don't let them send you there anymore.
I'll give you a cheque
for the debts I owe you.
OK, thanks.
Don't you want to play
with the dancing machine?
Yes.
Where's the dancing machine?
Over there, Boss.
Go with Boss.
It's always leaves
without saying, too cool
Forget it, don't think astray.
You go to play on!
This one is good.
You must keep to the beat.
You're bad, why didn't you help me?
I did tell you to follow the beat.
Brother, I'm back.
Breakfast.
Wipe the sweat.
I'm tired.
Last night...
after leaving the game centre.
...and where did you go?
Brother Sky ignored me,
so I went to disco.
For a dance?
I like dancing too.
Sorry.
You helped me out last time
but were sent to Girls' Home.
Brother, why you say that?
I can choose boyfriends,
but I can't choose a brother.
It's destined, don't say such a thing.
I'll kill whoever dare
say you're mentally retarded.
Will you?
Then...you'll be sent
to Girls' Home again?
You always fight for me.
I am upset for my dead parents...
...they passed away when I was young.
Brother, why are you so miserable?
I...
...I did finish high school.
but have you thought of...
...going back to school?
No way.
You know what good your school did you?
It let you meet Brother Sky.
You must be nuts.
You're underage,
and you want to woo Sky?
What do you mean?
My voice has changed already.
Right...a coarse voice indeed.
Why can't I love him?
I've thought over,
I won't go back to school.
but I'll become an apprentice in
your garage, like Big Head and Dee.
I want to learn how to repair cars.
Will...Sky employ you?
Help me persuade him.
Come on, help me persuade him.
Ask him for me, I'll buy you teddy bear.
Ask him for me, I don't need salary.
Don't bother me! Please...
Go away...
Please.
Paddy, 20kg in front, and 10kg
at the rear, increase by 2 bars.
and increase it to 460 hp.
But...it's been already fixed
with 4 brakes set.
It's getting out of control now.
The most I can do
is increase it by 1.5 bars.
...but the car will be controlling you...
I can always control cars.
Tell me, you can't or you refuse?
We've known for ages,
and I've never turned you down.
Please dissuade him for me.
Forget our friendship,
I'm boss, you will or won't modify it?
I ask you, will you modify it?
Sky!
What's it?
Stay out, it's men's topic, get upstairs
Get upstairs.
Will you modify it?
Will you?
I ask you, modify it or not?
OK, I'll modify it for you...
Will you modify it? I will
Trust me, I can control it.
OK, I'll modify it...
We're partners, we must trust each other.
Come on.
What about you guys?
Where is Sky?
We're in top condition tonight.
All left? They left long ago.
I should have taken a taxi here.
Who sat next to him?
His girlfriend, Kelly, you know her?
You want to take that seat?
If I hadn't arrived late,
it must have been me.
Brother...
What are you going to do now?
What's happened?
It's vital, today's race
is race of the century.
Tang Fung vs Sky, the track is from
Kwun Tong to Lung Cheung Road.
then up Castle Road to
Texaco Road junction.
Then u-turn and back
to the starting point.
Whoever reaches
there first is the winner.
Kelly!
It hurts! My legs are stuck!
Don't sit on, go and help!
A race never wins unless
he reaches the finale.
I'll rush to the finale now.
I'll pay you $1 million, OK?
Money is not all mighty.
Do me a favour, help me please!
I've never begged others,
please help me!
You must come out.
Help me, Sky!
Sky!
No alcohol taken, normal.
He's racing with Tang Fung,
of course he didn't drink.
All who take part in such underground
races will end up dying.
Is she out?
She's dead,
being under the battered car.
Sir, there's a tip-off.
I want you to come back
to the station with us.
Besides of charging you
with careless driving...
...we'll charge you
with possessing narcotics.
Take off shoes, put them over there.
KC, it's not a serious case indeed.
My son is only involved in an accident,
why no bail allowed?
Tony, call Eddy Hui,
their Commissionaire.
Yes
Mrs. Yu, we found 500 mg
of heroin in your son's car.
What?
My son is involved in narcotics?
I don't know.
No way, I must call up
Elsie Leung as well.
I'm sure someone wants to frame you!
$1 million, and side bet on limbs?
You want that now?
No! Help!
Sign here.
Thank you.
Sky...
How come?
I'm OK.
Did they beat you up?
Call for ambulance, quick.
Let's go home first.
Martin, mark down the time and location.
I must sue all cops here!
Yes, Mrs. Yu.
I ask you, aren't you policeman
to protect the citizens?
None of our business,
people in the custody beat him.
Let's go home.
Miss, what's up? What do you want?
Sky never touches narcotics,
someone must...
Leave my sister alone! Help!
Stop...
What do you mean?
What number are you?
Shut up! Stop fooling, OK?
Let's all go home first.
None of his business...
I'll take responsibility...
No...don't let them frame you...
Sky, come home with me!
Tell them you never possess narcotics!
Sky, tell them you're innocent!
Paddy need the medication again,
take it to him.
Sky, it hurts!
Elsie, I only have one son.
so please do me a favour.
Yes, I know, but it may be
interfering with justice, right?
Maybe it will, and maybe not.
We used to be school mates,
please help this time.
Give me a hand, please.
OK, I'll call you back later.
I know you are under pressure,
but there's a former case.
Anyway, I have good relation
with Mr. Tung.
OK, wait for your good news.
What did he say?
It's in vain, no need to call again!
Sky, your mom has made
all efforts already.
and it should be fine now.
I'm the one who commit a crime.
Don't worry, I won't get you involved.
Shut up!
It's not your affairs only,
we're both involved now.
If you were not my son,
I wouldn't care a dime.
Look at yourself.
I tell you, don't ever drive a car!
I don't want you to die like your dad!
My dad?
How did he die?
I remember you quarreled with him.
and you told me he disappeared,
soon you took me to his tomb.
You told me he was under there,
and wouldn't get up again.
Is he really dead? Is he?
I take him as if he were dead!
You take him as if he were dead?
He's alive?
You cheat me? Where is he?
Where is he?
I don't know!
Tony, arrange for him to leave HK.
I won't go unless I make it clear.
Your mom is right,
you'd better leave HK for the moment.
You want me to disappear?
I'll vanish this minute.
I won't ever come back.
Stand there!
Look at him...
I do have a secret,
even your mom doesn't know it.
I take your dad as idol.
Black Tone...is my father?
Black Tone is the real Dare Devil.
The century race between him
and Tang Fung.
...was breath-taking.
and there is never such a race anymore.
Every time when Black Tone won a race...
...he would give us a ride.
We each gave him $5,000.
Riding in his car from Princess Road
to Clear Water Bay
...was rare experience
You would never forget that experience.
I don't know whether it's out
of excitement or fear.
we wet our pants.
Go and find your dad in Thailand.
Is he in Thailand?
Someone saw him in Thailand years ago.
but don't know where exactly he is.
Granny.
Sky.
Kelly used to say she'd
take you to see me.
but she is dead now.
...and we finally meet each other.
Don't be sad.
I'm really sad.
But I don't have anymore tears.
She arrived from Taiwan 10 years ago....
...and lived with me since then.
and you're her only friend.
Look, it's quiet here...
She died in loneliness too.
Granny...
Take this.
There's something...that is priceless.
There's something we cannot
judge with money.
Go away! You needn't help me up!
Check which club possesses
the best girls.
Aren't we here to locate Sky?
Sky?...
Bangkok is so big,
it's not easy to find him.
Go and check, got it?
Yes.
One day how much?
B220 one day.
Ten days?
Uncle, how is everybody?
We're in trouble as your mom
is charging by the Attorney General.
Sorry.
You must use a false name
where're you go.
Cops are smart nowadays,
be careful for everything.
I have enough money with me.
I'll turn off my mobile phone
so cops can't detect my location.
Don't make a call even if it's necessary.
Uncle and your mom are eased
as you've grown up.
Don't worry, Uncle,
I will find my father.
OK, the line is impaired,
I must hang up now.
Bye.
Sky, where are you?
Police are looking for you everywhere.
Tell me, and I'll fly to see you.
No, I'm fine.
I'll contact you later.
Sky!
Brother Sky, where are you?
Brother and I will come to join you.
No, Nancy.
Remember to listen to your brother
and behave yourself.
I will.
Brother Sky, don't lose heart.
We both back you up.
Brother, try this pork.
You speak Cantonese?
I'm Cantonese.
Right, have you seen this guy?
No, sorry.
Help!
Thief!
What is it?
You're competent,
you have money to flee to Thailand?
All your money has been robbed.
Shall I give you $1 million
to go back to HK?
We did settle up our affairs
in HK already.
Damn you! Beat him!
Yes!
Catch him!
You broke my leg?
Syringe affected with Aids.
Let me give you injection
and you'll have HIV.
You want to revenge?
Get in the car, I come to help you,
get in...
Most guys fleeing here
from HK come for me.
So everyone here calls me King of Fleers.
I don't mean I must flee.
and those who flee here
call me King of Fleers.
You say you're so powerful.
...then can you find those robbers
and get back my money for me?
What if I can?
Report to the police?
Remember you are a culprit.
and you have lots of rivals in HK.
I want to see a doctor,
lend me some money.
You have valuable belongings?
I'll take it to pawn shop.
I have no money, but I'm rich in HK.
Lend me and I'll remit it to you.
You know why everyone who flees
to Thailand first?
The living standard is low in Thailand,
a little money lets you live like king.
I don't intend to spend my life here.
What do you want then?
I want to find this man.
Isn't he Black Tone?
You know him?
When he first came to Thailand,
everyone in HK thought he was dead.
He's still alive?
He's so horny, he won't die young.
Where is he now? He is my father.
I haven't seen him for 10 years now.
He's not in Bangkok.
He may be in Chingmai or in Pattaya.
You're really son of Black Tone?
Yes.
Here's some money.
It's sad on the flee, do take care.
Eat now.
Thanks.
Half cooked rice again?
It's a month now,
why don't you cooked the rice well?
I've asked you a whole month already.
Tell me where Sky is
if you want cooked rice.
I do want to say,
but Sky won't let me tell you.
He's not on a trip, he's on flee.
Can't we find him though he's fleeing?
You don't talk reason.
Paddy!
Nancy!
Uncooked rice?
Throw it, I've bought you good food.
Come, sushi, come, let's eat it.
You want to play a fool? What fool?
Stay calm...you both stay calm.
Don't be so snooty.
He beat you, brother.
Sorry you fix her.
Calm down.
Take it easy...
Paddy, my new boss, Tang Fung.
He likes your skills,
he wants you to modify cars for him.
then we can work together again.
That garage belongs to Sky.
I always tell you: Money is our boss.
and when Sky returns to HK,
you can go back to him.
Damn you!
Play a trick?
Beat my brother?
Stop fighting...
Stop...
Brother...Stop fighting...
Stop, calm down, listen to me
We are always like this
You play like this?
It's OK, we're always like this.
Don't think you're special.
if not Brother Fung wants you,
we won't come here.
What do you want?
Take it easy, Boss.
Tell Tang Fung I must revenge
for Sky and Kelly.
Tell me, remember! You ass-hole!
Beat it!
Brother...
I'm useless, I got a cramp
when I yelled at them.
Brother, you behaved very bravely.
You're the best mechanic
of modifying cars.
Let me cook you some tender rice.
Sky asked me to tell you.
...to behave yourself.
Sky, I must modify it into
the fastest car for you.
Paddy, I've left Bangkok, now on a bus.
...heading south.
I can't leave you any phone number.
How...about them?
That Tse is ass-hole!
He's real bastard, a real ass-hole!
Don't mention him anymore.
I've open...
a small garage in Yuen Long.
I'm now...
modifying the fastest car for you.
Come back and try it.
Wait till I come back.
Please take care of
Kelly's grandmother for me.
I will.
Anyway, you gave me all that money.
...to open my own garage.
It's your money, not mine.
I want to ask Uncle...
It's said they're in Canada,
and police are watching them closely.
Remember...
inform me if you have address.
I don't know where I am at present.
Have you seen this guy?
No.
You're from HK?
Yes.
He's from HK too, have you seen him?
Is he? I haven't seen him before.
Sky!
I want a haircut.
You're from HK?
Your hair is long,
sure you need a haircut.
Don't move!
Are you Black Tone?
You're Black Tone.
No, I'm not!
- Black Tone!
- I'm not!
You're Black Tone?
Stand there and don't move.
You're took me for someone else!
Black Tone, why did you cut
my son's hair like this?
Dad.
I'm Sky.
I've been looking for you.
Mom has been cheating me,
saying you're dead.
So many has happened to you?
Then Uncle asked me to find you here.
Tony?
He's a real nice guy.
Your mom is lucky to have him.
Since Tang Fung's incident,
I've brought them much trouble.
Do you have rivals with him?
Don't say it anymore!
Black Tone is dead,
don't mention the past again.
Don't keep saying you're dead.
Why do you bring me here?
Waiting for someone.
Pa!
This woman is my wife.
You needn't call her mother.
This kid is my son, he's called Blackie.
Wife
My son!
Honey, this is my son, no...
He's my friend.
How are you?
Have you greeted?
Honey, watch out, it's hot.
It smells good!
Honey, I'm happy.
Be careful.
It's tasty!
It's just like you.
Watch out.
It's hot.
My wife makes the perfect Hot Soup.
It's really hot and spicy.
Honey, come on, sit down...
Son, you keep watching TV all day,
and you smile whenever I talk to you,
and you never remember
the Cantonese I teach you.
You're half Chinese, you know?
Honey, you want to smile too?
You want it day and night, don't you?
Son, you like these dishes?
Yes
It's habit in Thailand,
same dishes for lunch and dinner.
It's not as varied as in HK.
See how much I earn today.
Look.
What are you doing?
Nothing, I want to see
how much I earn today.
Not much, about 100 Baht.
My wife...I think it's about 200 Baht.
So little?
It's enough for the 3 of us.
300 Baht a day, it's HK$3,000 a month.
It's enough, it's not HK here.
When in HK, the money
I spent one night...
is enough for few year expenses here.
The money I spent on modifying cars
is enough for my whole life here.
You know, your mom is rich, right?
Your mom always buys you cars.
and each costs $1 million, right?
You needn't go to work today?
How to make a living?
There aren't many kids
in Pattaya that need haircut.
so you ask her to work
and make money for you?
That's why I married her.
I'm a pimp, right?
Why are you like this?
Don't mention it, I'm disabled now.
How come?
Nothing, here is OK
Look.
I know, it was so noisy
last night that I couldn't sleep.
Of course it was noisy...
Are you impotent?
Of course not.
Of course I can, it's not the same, son.
This is...
I teach you because you're my son.
I didn't steal it...
What is it? Take it easy.
She stole my watch while I was sleeping.
I didn't...
I'll have her arrested if
she doesn't return my Rolex to me.
Man, my wife says
she didn't steal your watch.
She never tells lies.
Give me back my watch.
You mean I frame her?
Do you know who's
most furious in Pattaya?
Man, give me 2 days' time.
OK, I'll give you 2 days.
Come to see me at
Thai Boxing Gym in 2 days.
Let's go!
Dad.
Do you find me useless?
I just don't understand.
Uncle said you were famous
in Princess Road racing.
I am so proud of it.
because that Black Tone is my father.
That Black Tone is dead.
He's alive, he's sitting in front of me.
but he became another person.
Yes, I'm another person now.
I'm called Black Tong now.
You're still young, you can start again.
But you never fight back
when others bully you.
Right, because I'm disabled now.
so I left HK.
and gave the title
of Dare Devil to Tang Fung.
Tang Fung and I had
2 races on Princess Road.
and he wasn't up to me.
so they all called me Dare Devil.
I'm the Underground
Champion of Car Racing.
Tang Fung sent his men
to give me money.
They took me to Macau and fevered...
and that's why your mother left me.
Once, I lost $5 million in Casino Lisboa
and this bastard Tang Fung
challenged me
saying if I won,
he would pay off debts for me
and if I lost, he would break
my left arm and right leg
so this is it.
Have you figured out why you lost?
I didn't figure out why I lost.
I used to be snooty.
I spent money whatever I liked.
I stressed on car modification
and not driving skills.
My friend Paddy advised me
not to make ample modification.
but I didn't listen.
He says ample modification
makes the car control me.
but I ignore his advice, so...
Right.
Do you want to revenge for me?
Though I'm disabled,
I can become your instructor.
How is it? I'm up there too, come on.
But you...
You're in the car, you must calculate
...using 3rd gear, then down
to 2nd gear to turn this turnoff.
Son, remember that moustache?
If you defeat him.
they'll forgive my wife's
stealing the Rolex.
Who is this guy?
This is the Dare Devil in Thailand.
He was 3 time champion in Thailand.
He represents Thailand going on
Formulae race as well.
He's ranked 48 worldwide.
I must lose then, you want me to die?
Of course not.
It was all the past.
He belonged to the 80s, like I did.
You know, you and I
are 2 generation of the Dare Devil.
So you won't lose
Come on, driving such a car?
Yeah, so you must use your skills.
Ranked 48?
I really didn't steal the watch.
Son, my wife said
she didn't steal the watch.
Whether she did or not, I must race.
But I never thought I would race
for the sake of a Rolex.
Have you thought of
how to defeat the 48th?
Yes, to drive faster than him...
How to drive faster than him?
Then teach me, you're my instructor.
Without brake and you'll be fast.
Don't let the speedometer threatens you.
You said it, we must overcome our fear.
so you must prove it yourself.
Racing requires a good car,
but good skills as well.
Son, you can make it.
Take this 10 bucks.
My face is on it.
It's a lucky money.
Remember, like this.
Bo Bo, let's go.
It's dangerous for him.
Yes, but I can't help.
Only this can help him overcome his fear
His fear, you understand?
I know, but he's your son,
if anything happens...
Right, he's my son on the track.
Even if he dies,
I still have another son.
If you like, we can have
more children, right?
You smile, I need it whenever you smile.
Don't let the speedometer scare
you if you want speed.
You must prove yourself
to overcome the fear.
Sorry, I've found my watch.
Man, why didn't you tell me earlier.
What?
Nothing, he said he'd found his watch.
Get me wine, I must drink with them.
Let's cheers!
Cheers!
You're Black Tong?
I want Black Tone, from HK!
You bastard!
How are you? Come back to HK with me!
What?
OK?
No, just like today.
Go back and race on Princess Road!
I won't!
No, sit still, man!
You must care for your health.
I can't help, the garage is just opened.
I must...get more business.
Look at you, you cough hard.
Brother, let's go.
Take the medicine too, why so hurry?
Where are you going?
Where's Brother Sky? Not return yet?
I don't know you well.
You want both legs broken this time?
Nancy, Maddie does care about Sky.
Just like me,
I care about my ex-boss too.
You make him flee, you care about him?
Ass-hole!
Don't beat my brother!
I wonder why Sky employ you,
you stammering guy
Boss, don't be mad.
I know you're expert at modifying cars,
how about your driving skill?
My race with Sky didn't finish yet...
...as he fell off fly-over,
and never reached the finale.
I don't take it as a victory.
Dare you have a race with me?
Brother, he's daring you.
I never race with stupid guys.
but I respect you as you're Sky's man.
If you want to defeat me
to revenge for him.
I'll have a race with you any time.
Boss, we have to go to dinner, come on.
My brother is proved
to have HIV positive.
If you don't want,
I'll wait till Sky comes back.
I must have a race
to revenge for my brother.
I promise you.
Brother, no, they're daring you only.
I promise you!
I want to test your judgment,
your guts and your skills.
You rush forward till you
reach the end of the pier.
and brake hard, see if you can do it
I didn't ask you to drive into the sea
Get down.
Jump!
Tone, a girl comes to see your son.
Brother Sky...
This is my first flight ever...
I know nothing,
I don't speak English, or Thai
but I come here with the address
you gave me last time.
I want to ask you, why are you here?
Where's your brother?
Brother promised to race with Tang Fung.
but the stake is life.
Why must your brother race
with Tang Fung?
Why must you push me away from you?
Can I hold you for longer time?
But I'm all wet.
I don't mind!
Try and dissuade my brother
to go for the race.
Say it slowly, why must your brother
race with Tang Fung?
Your new girlfriend? You lucky guy.
No, nuts.
She's sister of my buddy.
Sister of your buddy?
I think she's not mature yet.
She must have something to come
all the way here for you, right?
No.
You still miss the girl who died?
But she's already dead, right?
Don't think about her anymore.
Sky?
Want to know why I call you Sky,
and not Brother Sky?
You're still a little girl,
don't think astray.
You still take her as a little girl?
Brother Sky.
What is it?
I want to tell you something.
After midnight tonight
will be my birthday.
I'm 18 then.
I won't fight anymore.
as I'm over age for Girls' Home.
if I commit anything,
I'll be sent to jail.
I might die.
OK, it's good for you
to think of your future.
So please don't take me
as a little girl again.
Come to see the moon.
Sorry, did I wake you up?
You are misunderstanding.
We're not making love, we're...
...doing Thai massage,
my wife is a masseuse
It's painful yet comfortable.
Little girl, come here.
My wife is expert, want to try?
No? Honey, let's go on.
Take your time, we'll go.
Sister, buy flowers.
It's your birthday?
Yes
No, these are...
So old fashioned.
Want them or not?
You really don't want to go back to HK?
I'm called Black Tong,
and here is my paradise.
HK no longer belongs to me.
I've thought it over,
if it is not for my buddy, Paddy.
...I won't go back to HK.
I want to get marry here and live here.
I want to count the money
which I make everyday.
Control your car accurately is
important while you're driving.
You must learn to use brake.
...as you failed to use brake
so you drove into the sea.
Sometimes it's right.
Sometimes you must use brake,
sometimes the accelerator.
Some racers don't care about dying.
but I'm old.
I'm disabled, I should retire now.
but you are young,
you still have a long way to go.
so you must accelerate.
Son, return to HK
and create your own world.
You'll make it.
Thanks, dad.
No thanks, I've never been a good father
Bye, Brother...
Bye, Black Tone!
Remember...
Remember what I've taught you!
Damn it!
Brother.
Defeat him for me!
Again!
Paddy.
Forget it, let's wait till Sky
comes back here.
Paddy, you're my buddy,
I don't want anything happen to you.
Buddy?
If Sky returns, the first he'll do is
...to settle up with you.
Kid, Brother Fung
wants a special treat, dare you?
Idiot.
You dare not?
Mechanic...
No, don't go mad like him
You can back out this minute
Brother.
Nancy, I've decided
to race with Tang Fung.
as I must get back my ego.
I don't want others to look down on me.
It's good idea you become apprentice,
but you must go to school.
It's not bad for you to love Sky,
but wait till you grow up.
Be good, brother, Paddy.
Big Head, where's my brother?
That bastard Tang Fung insisted
on racing last night,
but Paddy's car capsized.
He got trapped in the car.
Come, we're at the mortuary.
Where's my brother?
Brother!
Brother...
Why come here? You traitor, go away!
Go away, traitor! Sorry...
I...did ask Paddy to back out.
Go away, he doesn't want to see you!
I never expected he'd die...
I really didn't know this would happen.
Go and explain to him, go!
Paddy...
Sorry.
I asked you to back out.
I really don't know this...
I don't want to lose a friend.
Get an appointment with Tang Fung, go.
Take my condolence, don't cry.
I'm not crying!
My brother left this,
but I can't open, help me.
It's like a note of Maths?
Let me see.
No, it's notes of how to modify cars.
Paddy's theory of modifying cars.
With this note...
You have confidence?
No problem.
Sure!
Let's not waste his efforts.
Brother, I know you'll help us.
You must bless Brother Sky
to defeat Tang Fung.
Sky, the car is in excellent condition.
Hey, does brother's note help?
Does it help?
The sprat parts are not enough.
We miss some gears, and axles too.
What is it?
We miss some spare parts.
The computer is not the type
which mechanic said.
The 4 spring are impaired too,
this won't work.
Don't bullshit, let me steal one back.
What have I said?
What is it?
Here is a carton, what is inside?
That's the gears and axles we need,
all brand new.
You ordered them?
Even the computer is new.
Does Santa Claus send them to us?
Don't bullshit!
I won't accept things from that bastard!
Come out!
I hope this Christmas present will help.
You stole them?
I stole from you.
You know you used to spend like king?
You bought numerous spare parts.
so me and Paddy built a secret drawer,
and hide these spare parts,
wanting to sell them for cash.
Now you need them,
of course I must give them back to you.
I won't let that Tang Fung have them.
Move them in, no need to say thank you.
Come in, Santa Claus.
Help modify the car.
Boss, you're tired?
Leg massage.
This part talks about nitrogen speeding.
As nitrogen is 3 times
more powerful than gasoline.
so nitrogen can increase
the explosive power.
Yet, the time must not exceed 10 seconds
Remember, you control the car.
Turbo, inter cooler, 4-wheel drive.
This is a super car ever modified.
It suits you most.
Whatever how stupid the opponent is...
...I must race with all
I might have to face.
It's on fire!
Take it away, it's nitrogen,
it'll explode!
Use fire extinguisher!
Is it alright? It's alright
It's the last can.
Sorry.
Racing wheel,
suspending shock absorbers.
AP break disk,
titanium alloy exhausted pipe.
Isn't it a bit too much?
Do you know the dividend on you?
It's 10 times, so I'll try my best.
After I left the jail, I told myself.
I mustn't lose again.
Brother, I promise
I won't be bad anymore.
I must be a fair lady,
I must listen to Brother Sky.
Who are you talking to?
With my brother.
Before the launching of this toy.
I found brother like a panda.
but since it's launched, look
it looks like my brother a lot
Get up here.
Me?
Do you know I never buy toys?
As I find they worthless.
But there's something
you can buy with money.
Don't say so, this toy is expensive.
Want to sit next to me?
You let me sit next to you?
I must revenge for my brother.
How to? I'm the driver.
Come on, let's do some practice.
Sit still.
OK.
Hold your brother tightly.
Come, 1st gear.
Turn left!
Then right.
Left!
You really not scared?
No.
OK.
Aren't they here yet?
That bastard must be too afraid to come.
No, Sky is not such a guy.
Both his father and
himself aren't such guys
Tonight, the dividend
for Brother Fung is 1 to 1
and that bastard is 1 to 5
You drive this lousy car?
You'll surely lose!
We fear nothing, as you don't fear Aids.
So you're uneducated.
There's a saying:
Tools are vital for a success.
Car racing requires for driving skills.
But tools are important as well.
I tell you, I have enough tools today.
Is Black Tone fine?
I tell you, I'll defeat you,
just as I defeated your father.
I tell you too,
Black Tone sends you his regards.
He wants me to tell you
he lives like king in Thailand.
Good.
And my buddy, Paddy.
Sky, the car is in excellent condition.
Brother will bless you
to defeat that bastard.
Be gentle.
Sorry.
Give it to me.
- You gave me that
- Give it to me now.
Lucky.
Take it.
Kelly's
Remember, you are to control the car.
Some racers don't care about dying.
Sometimes you must use brake,
sometimes the accelerator.
Why I can't even see his rear lights?